Oh,
my daddy says that life comes at you fast we are
like blades of grass we come to prime and in time we just wither
away and it all changes my view with a looking glass
won't catch pass only photographs from mind us
of the passing days. Oh, nothing stay
the same from yesterday. See, I recall being
afraid of the dark and holding on a
teddy bear. Got to wrap myself in blankets just to cover
me. From fears that was in and now I'm here
and the night is mine to hear me free I
was too young to understand what it means.
I couldn't wait till I could be 17.
I fought it like when he said, take my time to dream
now I wish I could freeze the time at 17 oh
now I wish I could freeze the time at seven. My mother
said, don't forget where you come from, where you've
been. Always keep your closest friends they can't slip away.
They keep you grounded. Oh, keep yourself surrounded
with good advice and yeah, I guess that sounded nice when
I was ten. Over never were the true
words in all my days I've ever heard? And when she told
me little girl answer is love to those words
that I keep with me don't even change so quickly?
Keep buried in my heart I never thought
dream me free I was
too young to understand what it means.
I couldn't wait till I could be 17.
I thought you, like, take my time.
Breathe now.
I wish I could freeze the time. It's everything I've
been going on. I've been going.
I'm in the I don't know enough.
See, I was racing and waiting for that day that I would be old
enough. Guess I'll be facing and pace myself.
Gotta prepare for when growing up. I was
too young. To understand what it means.
I could always be 17.
I thought she like what she said. Take my time to breathe.
Now I wish I could freeze the time at 1717.
Oh, um now
I wish I could freeze the time at 17.