It. I taught myself how to move.
I'm not the type that can find you stupid
next to I love you.
No. So what can you show me
that my heart don't know already. We make
our own set. You're? Qualified in Michigan.
What can you show me that my heart don't
know already we make our own sense
and you're qualified in my eyes
and you're qualified in my eyes I'm
qualified only
losers go to school.
They can't. Teach what they can't prove can't
put this inside a test tube because
stupid's next to I love you so
why can you show and my heart don't know
already? We make our own sense
you're qualified in me what? Can you
show and my heart don't know already we
make our own you're qualified in
my and
you're qualified in my love
your qualify and now that
we're all grown up what
we do? And now
that we come we
did it all alone now we're coming on the
throne we did it all alone now
we're coming on the throne and now we
all came up do we lose?
Do we lose?
So can you show me that my heart don't
know already? Because we make our own sense
and you're qualified me what can you
show me now my heart don't know already
because we make our own sense and you're
qualified to me jesus,
don't let
and you're qualifying.