Shit. You motherfucker right I'm the bitch that's keeping it live and keeping it
hot when you punk ass niggas don't nigga west Side what?
Bring it on look for me lost in the Whirlwind
96 Bonnie and Clyde me and my girlfriend doing native Father
we rise up in this world of sin born as a kettle chap waving
this worldwide come on. I've showered years recalling tears
heart lace with venom smoke insurance, drinking more lick the father
forgive us me and my girlfriend must have fell in love with the struggle.
Hands on the steering wheel watch me bail out bustle. Fuck them
all. Watch the phone screaming automatic gunfire exercising all
demons my bumpy, yo so gates and high ready to
die we bail out to take the jail back niggas unite our first
day can wait to see you naked touch you with every secret place I
can hardly wait to bust freely got you rare you so happy
to see make the front page prime time live on TV nigga my
girlfriend maybe 45, but she still lie one shot
making Niggas heartbeat stop what? I'm busting on you
pocket niggas run, nigga, run I'm on your ass, nigga run,
niggas suck it hot nigga run
nigga, yeah. West side die,
nigga, die my girlfriend block it in the darkest night when
Nick is that bitch made she got the heart to fight nick of my girlfriend
but we separated at times I knew deep inside, baby girl always
be mine. Picked you up when you was not sorted out. My life a crime
with you. Want you some sales when you turn 22. It's true.
Nothing compares to the satisfaction that I feel when we outmash
me. And my girlfriend all I need in this life is safe?
It's me and my girlfriend down the rise
of the bloody end? Just me and my girlfriend all
I need in this life is safe is me and my girlfriend
down the rise of the bloody end see
my girlfriend I was too immature to understand your ways
and experience back in the days caused so many arguments and straits now
I realize I treat you the secret to keep it being fable now
sleep. Sleep. We closer than the hands of town. Deeper than
the driver. Mankind. I trust you, dearly. I shoot blind.
It's how my clock figures dropping. Niggas as we rise.
We are soldiers in. God's eyes now it's time for war never leave
me, baby I'm paranoid sleeping with you loaded by my bedside
crazy tell us when you hang with the fellas I wait patiently alone
anticipating what? I'm going to come home. I'm waiting by the phone.
This is true love I'm feeling. Had a lot of women in my bed
with you to finish. If you ever need me, call. I'll be there. Do it
all. You're the reason not to. Stand tall? Me and my
girlfriend all I need in this life
is my girlfriend down
the ride to the bloody A my girlfriend
I love finger fucking you all of a sudden I'm hearing thunder when
you bust a nut nick is be ducking or taking numbers. Let her watch you
at a block party begging for drama. Why don't leasing on the old Thomas?
And so my mama I would trade my life with yours behind closed
doors. The only girl that I know everything I'm asking for, talking to
me, begging me to just take you around 17 like brandy.
You just want to be down talking loud when I tell you be quiet.
You move the crowd busting rounds, activating the ride that's why I love
you so no control down the road unleashed after a hit,
you break apart the back of one piece much love to my one and
only girlfriend. The world is ours just hold me down,
baby witness the problem never leave a nickel alone I love you black
or chrome turn this house into a happy home me and my girlfriend
all I need in this life is safe down
the ride to the bloody all
I need in this life is safe. My girlfriend
down the body to the blood.
My girlfriend lost in the world
with 96 body club. Me and my girlfriend to
one day probably ride up in this world with Born as a ghetto
chat. Raised in the world with look for me. Lost in
the world with 96 running your cloud. Me and my girlfriend doing
85 of our dropping this water sit. Born.
As a get up chat. Raised in this world with look for me.
Lost in the world with 96 running a cloud.
Me and my girlfriend doing 85 but we rise up in this water
sit. Born as a get. Up chat raising this world with look
for me. Lost in the world with 96 brownie cloud
me and my girlfriend. Lost in the world with 96
money. You cloud me and my girlfriend. Meet my girlfriend.