Big sight new tank y'all
know how to go, you know all eyes on me roll
up in the club all eyes on me
all eyes on me you
know what? I bet you got it twisted. You don't know who to trust.
So many playing, hating nick is trying to sound like us. Say they ready for
the bumble and I don't think they know it straight to the depths. Of hell
is where the cab is going. Well all you steal down nick a hollow when
you see me and let the devil suck for the day. They finally freed me.
I got a camera band of nickels every. Time we ride hitting motherfuckers
up when we pass by until I die later life of a false player because
even when I'm hot fuck with me and get boss later the features in my
eyes because all I want is cast and things are five double low being
smoking flashy brains bitches pursue me like the dream been known to
disappear before your office like a dope thing it seems my main thing was
to be major paid the game shopper than the motherfucking. Raise the
blade, save money, bring bitches. Bitches bring lies. One nick
is getting jealous and motherfuckers die. Depend on me. Like the first and fifth
thing they might hold me for the second buffy. Folks won't get me we got
foe, nickels and low rise and ski mask screaming thug life every
time they pass all eyes on me little life of thug nigga till
a day adopt little life of the boss play all eyes on
all eyes on me little life of the Doug nigga till the day I die
because even getting hot hey to
my Nigga pocket so much trouble in
the world nigger can't nobody feel your pain the world's
changing every day times moving fast? My girl said I need a race
alone when she lasts? I'm called between my woman and my pistol with
my chips triple being got some smokers on whistle as a dip I'm
lost in the land with no plan living life flawless crime balls contraband
let me toss this mediocre's. Got a lot of nerve. Let my
bucket swerve. I'm taking off from the curve. The nervousness neglect
made me pack a tech devoted to serving this my wet and
paid checks like a kite satellite. Nigga, I'm forever bowling.
It ain't right. Parasites, triggers and fleas crawling sucker duck and
get busted. No emotion. My devotion is handling my business nigga,
keep on coasting. Where you going? I've been there came back as lonely homie steady
flowing against the grave niggas still don't know me it's about the money in this
rap shit, this crap shit, it ain't funny niggas don't even know how to act
shit, what can I do? What can I say? Is there another way?
Blessing shit all day 24 parlay my little homie G can't
you see I'm buster free? Niggas can't stand me all eyes on me?
All eyes on me?
All eyes on me? Little life of the duck nigga until the day
I die? Little life of a bros play? All eyes on me?
The fans just watch it? Nick is plotting to get me? Will I survive?
Will I die? Come on, let's pitch it a possibility? Giving me jobs?
Lawyers making the grip? I told the judge I was wasteful? That's why Blake
shit was hyper? As a kid? As a teenager on my mobile
calling big shot on a team major packing hundreds in my draws?
Fuck the law, bitches I fuck with a pass and I'm living rough and raw?
Catch a case instead of fast rain bowling in the fast lane? Hustle to
the morning never stop until the Cascade? Live my life as a Thug Nick till
the day I die? Live my life as a Paul's player? Because even getting hot
these niggas got me tossing shit? I put the top down now it's time
to floss my shit? Keep your head up, nigga mickey motherfucker suffer up
in the beans burning rubber? The money is Manitob the holes but strap
the swimming new lights down? He cook with the bulletproof vet make sure
y'all is on the meal ticket? Get your money, motherfucker let's get rich
and wheel kick it? All eyes on me later? Life is a Doug,
niggas? Until the day I die? Little life is a false play? All eyes
on me?
All eyes on me? Little life is a Doug, niggas? Until the
day I die? Little life is a false play? All eyes on me?
All eyes on me?
Pay attention, my nigga? See how that shit go?
Nigga walk up in this motherfucker be like Ping till
the day I die? Because even getting hot
every motherfucking, I got busted toes?
Police watching, you know,
like, what they think I'm walking around with some keys in my pocket?
They think I'm going back to jail? Ain't really on that dope lemon
like it's Thug Nick till the day adopt? I know y'all watch play?
I know y'all got me in the scope? I know y'all notice
like I got
me on the smell of me but I'm knowing.