Amen. You a little stuck up. A love word
of love. I should have seen
you juggle right from the start. Taught me so many lessons.
How not to mess with broken hearts. So many questions. When this began, we was
the perfect match. Perhaps we had some problems, but we were getting at it and
now the arguments are getting loud. I want to stay, but I can't help
them walking out. So we're the way. Just take my hand and understand
if you could see I never planned to be your man. It just wasn't
me. But now I'm searching for commitment and other arms. I want to
shelter you from home. Don't be alarm. Your attitude was the
call you got me stressing soon as I opened up the door with your jealous
questions like wicked I be you're killing me with your jealousy
never mind vicious to be free I can't breathe as soon as I leave
it's like a trap I hear you calling me to come back I'm a sucker
for love but
you don't what you won't
do, you won't do you
tried everything but you don't just
when I thought I broke away and I'm feeling happy you try to trap me
say you're pregnant and guess who's? The daddy don't want to fall for it but
in this case what could I do? So now I'm back to making promises to
you trying to keep it true what if I'm wrong? A trip to keep me
on and on. Trying to be strong in the process. Keep it going. About to
lose my composure. I'm getting close to packing up and leaving notes
and getting ghosts. Tell me, who knows a piece of place where I can go
to climb my head I'm feeling low, losing control my heart is hanging
leave or what a tangle where we weave when we conspire to conceive?
And now you're getting calls at the house. Guess you're cheating. That's all I need
to hear because I'm leaving. I'm out the dope never know more when
you see me. This is the end because now I know you've been cheating I'm
just tears
on your pillow when you steal steak as you sit and pray hoping the beatings
would go away it wasn't always a hit and rumble relationship. It used to be
love, happiness and companionship. Remember when I treated
you good? I moved you up to the hills out the eels of the ghetto
hood. Me and you a happy home. When it was on,
I had a lot to call my own, I feel but I
was lost trapping your eyes. Biocha power getting tossed. No need.
A lie. You had a man and I knew it. You told me. Don't worry
about it. We can do it now. But the pressure. Make a decision because I'm
waiting. When I'm alone I'm on the phone having secret conversations
I want to take a misery replace it with happiness but I need your faith
in me what
you try to name so
you ain't right you won't do
you tried everything but you don't know
you tried
everything you don't what
you won't do you
try to every little bit you
try.