My life be like y'all
know what this is my life be like oh, yeah, by the way,
this is the remix whoa.
My life be like my
life be like I'm like my
I even break sacrifice
in the right living like a fingertip sometimes
I won't, I said, yeah,
I can run faster than that because my ass
I'm in traffic. Will it be traffic? I'm coming down the corner like a magic
doing 90 on the freeway and hit the switches in the high speed chase
with these pump bitch. Don't turn around. I ain't giving up because they don't worry
me pussy ass. Better blurry me running out of gas.
I'm the pocket, I'm on the hood how to fuck they go?
Catch a cook. I got away because of leather
my neighbors for a favor now, you know play a sick endeavor. I watch the
sea from the rooftop movie at the copper step assuming
right,
they bleed. Come two pussies, they wit just making a threesome.
They growing up quick you got to buy your seat gun now they spread magazine.
For they could read one. I'm thinking short range. Give me a sport range.
When it get warmer. I'm jumping in the storm duck when I'm
passing by, put your head between your legs she show asset by Demon
Break sacrifices the
price living like a fingertip sometimes
I fall I said you
niggas lost your game? I'm throwing a rock down just to put your D I'm
back with a block now running your mouth to our shit all in it.
All your ass. And I'm about to dig all in it. I burped
you, niggas. I fed and I burped you niggas. Quickest that I will earth
you niggas. Clothed, you, niggas. Wipe the snot from the nose. Of you niggas want
not to expose you niggas fist knife will raise a fight I got a year
in a day still played it like they gave me life can't walk through the
jail without shackles and too hot throwing shit on a ward not like
demon break my tour when I pray like
a fingertip sometimes I fall out
follow me a man a lot of states I gotta pay my fucking bills so
I'm transporting weight take my place to pick up my nickel and now we rolling
drop the keys like they stolen tell me, who do you fear? I'm out
of town to the coast is clear enough to last a year they got me
running from the police nowhere to go with the lights up rolling down
the dirt road but I ain't going alive I'd rather try to be a comic
I rather fire on my target I hit the corner doing 90 all
sick, some bitches right behind me please
don't mind sacrifice
in the price sometimes
I fall out of the
things I like yo, I got guns from Italy smoke trees considerably mid state
and crane it seems as where all my niggas be the ghetto misery, shootouts and
liquor stores a perpendicular angle of the clout war police searching
up Alexo but who's petrol my tech blow straight off the roof to test your
respect over dodo respect me, it got me handcuffed to rough life I just
be up nice breathing with scuff knife pour my beers, pull my peoples
under the stairs these years I got their names in my swears popping twist down
like it's my first child liquor shop holiday style rock and steel
sweaters wallet be down like me that make me say
loud sacrifices the price living like a
fingertip sometimes I fall out
like you bounce
now hands up, you know how we do we make the club jump everywhere
we go it's no secret, everybody know when Drake's
involved there's plenty of money involved and plenty honeys involved. It's sunny Sundays
and palm trees cali. Every day is just another party from the valleys
all the way to the Mate Mile Alleys. Let's rally. Hands up for the grand
finale now Ray is about to speak drain's about to speak plays about
the weed six days about the week you could catch me in the studio banging
out the beast provide you with the heat to keep blazing out the speaker so
never say never CAS Shady at the Mask together along with your unit record presents
the return of the knock and shit no one can do it better we set
a club up and leave without a shredder evidence that still
aftermath come on,
Dr Dre. We ain't leaving. Let go.
Sacrifices. The price. My life.
Sometimes I fall I said yeah,
not to put the Bible. Think I like me like I'm like a
price is a price.
Sometimes I fall out like
you try not to put the Bible things I like. Me like it.
My life be like I'll figure something again.
My life be like my
life be like my
life be like.