And it's like the hook goes something we all adore.
It's the one thing worth dying for nothing
but pain stuck in this game searching for fortune
and fame something we all adore.
The one thing we dying for nothing.
But pain. Stuck in this game searching for fortune and fame.
That's what I hear. And my nigga say we want the fame.
Come on. Come on. One thing
we all adore something worth dying
for. Nothing but pain. Sucking this
game, searching for fortune and fame.
The one thing we all adore. Something worth
dying for. Nothing but pain.
Stuck in this game, searching for so we exist and breathe.
Some believe. Comer see. Comes to g stresses after.
Battle with success comes greed they got me hot when they shot me plotted my
revenge to increase my end enemies getting dropped winner
lose red or blue we must all stay true play the game,
nigga never let the game play you looking for the fame niggas change fast
that's a shame what's the gang lost those who controls our brain who
cannot blame? The world seems strange at times someone insane
I'm hoping we can change with time I'm living blinded searching for refinement
curse I know death follows me but I murder him first and
worse yet with these breath steps I take reflex instead
of jealous bastards with my ski mask I'm the first one to
warn them blasted, wrapped in plastic bullshit and got his ass
hit ain't nothing left now treated like a step chad was
not for me nothing but busters and bitches be rocking beats fakes
we throw them back like hard walls without the gloves no love for these fake
desperate thugs I plead the heavy smoking blowout they bless it
for henny drunk nights and hot days cocking my heat shooting the sideways a life
on a run full of coming plus unconditionally married to my gun fulfilling my
destiny all needs and one desires be pulling all my cabbage
like fire stuck in the trance searching for something higher fortunate
fame one thing we
all adore something worth dying
for nothing but pain stuck in this
game searching for fortune fortune and fame lost
in the rain a loss in the game your life is the cost of the
game we forcing the change motherfuck lost in the chain
all of the blame belongs to the part of the brain that will never
use nigga plus my heart and plus my heart and if I ever lose homie
better matter to better matter to you and
your family come before all the fortune of fame as I walk
up in the crib late to rest my head say some moms to the angels
hope they bless my bed hope they bless me in a righteous way got
to hold me locked down out of town I send them a kite to say
man I hate in your heart you need to clist it dog praying for
my downfall and I consistent dog I was passed down the
street fame like clock locks to keep aim was raised up with a clock rocks
that I ran with the local street game they say the lightest thing will still
shine in the dark you can't have easy been a man but choose a boy
in your heart and that's a game that I got from generation of game in
the bowl to light dog we need to switch up lanes think about
it one thing we all adore something
worth dying for nothing but pain
stuck in this game searching for fortune and fame
one thing we all adore something worth dying
for nothing but pain stuck in this game
searching for fortune complain I see my fair share the
fame, it won't change me now I got this piece of change I
feel strange I got so used to the hood that when I finally got
out at first it ain't feel good I was the baby still retarded
from slavery when we struggled and shell shit ain't nobody saved me
getaway made me I made myself poverty
raped me thinking ain't no help. I pray for my health, my mind and my
family too fail myself, my grind and my family crew where
one hand washes the other. No, we ain't blood, but we
still real brothers. The struggle is real. Nothing could still what
we build when that remains the same to the day that we kill
that's real life. I was named to be loved by my
family tree that made to me. How about it?
One thing we all adore something worth
dying for nothing will pain.
Stuck in this game searching for fortune and fame.
One thing we all adore something
we're dying for nothing them for pain.
Stuck in this game searching for fortune and fame.
We all want money and riches. We all want to find a lot of life.
From the most heartless gang banger to the most virtuous
police officer.