Know what you heard about me what if you can't get a
dollar out of me? No gotta let, no birds you can't see
then I'm A-V-I am free I don't
know what you heard about me what if she can't get
a dollar out of me? No gotta let no birds you can't see
then I'm sorry. She in the
club, she dances for dollars. She got a tank for that gucci, that fendi,
that prada, that beastie, beachy ball, berry, dosing, kapana.
She feed them fool's fantasies. They pay her cause they wanna. I spit a little
G man in my gang gotta owl it. Had her ass up
in the Ramada some trick talking in the ear saying they think about her.
I got a bite but a boss trying to get a drink about her.
She liked my stash, she liked my smash, she liked the way I talk.
She from the country then she liked me because I'm from New York. I ain't
that trying to holler because I want some I'm not trying
to holler because I want some bread. I could care less how she perform when
she in the bed may hit that track, catch a date and come and pay
the kid. Look baby, this is simple. You can't see roll up
would be you roll up with A-P-I-M-P-I
don't know what you heard about me. What if you can't get
a dollar out of me? No kind of like no permits you can't
see then I'm A-P-I-M-I
bring you the chosen one, Big Jeffrey.
Now players, I got some fresh game to bring to the table
today. Now this player right here, he's different. He don't
drive a Cadillac, he don't got a Perm.
Why should we let you in the Pimp Legion of Doom, man.
Whoever said progress was a slow process? Wasn't talking about me. I'm A-P-I-M-P.
Plus I got the magic stick.
Fiftytent and S noo
P don't be styling your map book of 2003.
And y'all know I'm from the PPG.
F-I-F-T-Y-C-E-N-T-M-S-N-W-O-P.
We internationally known and locally respected.
What you know about me? Yeah, girl, I got my now lady gator zone
I'm about to show you how my pimp hand is way strong you're dead
wrong if you think the pimping going die twelve piece water honey
chicks by my side I'm down with that boy fit that like I'm
down with Blue we love you, Snoop Dogg. Yeah, I love you too,
cheap. You and I tizzy rolling with me
and the deep big tissue. My partners in New York. No. Hot doggy,
get down. I got my riders in Queen got some freaks uptown.
I got my business in Manhattan and I ain't around. I got
some butter pecan Puerto Ricans from the boogie down that's
waiting on me to return so they can snatch these braids out and put my
hair in a perm word. They love it when I gets
to limping and spitting this mac and magnificent pimping.
I don't know what you heard about me.
What if you can't get a doll out of Merch
over and ride with a Star? Did it get you far? I'm A-P-I-M-B-G-A-N-G-S-E-R.
I'm young, but I ain't dumb there's some tricks, but I ain't one I'm a
gorilla for stroller I trippy and try to run I let them. Do as they
please as long as they get my cheese. Even if they got a freeze or
it's 100 degrees, I keep them on it. Take a look under my sleeve.
I ain't got to give them much. They happy with Mickey. We keep
it pippin in the south. You know how I go. We drive old school
white walls with me flow. I spend the G unit peace and get them dizzy.
Handcuff up your love or your girl coming with me. When your neck
and wrist clothes she already should know the money make the world go
round so let's get more it's time to show these players how it should be
done. You got pimple kitchen. You might could be one I
don't know what you heard about me but if you can't
get a dollar out of me look at it like no birds you can't see
well, Pippa can't say, don't down him, crown him. Preach.
Preach. Have a knot,
yeah. Hollywood said there's no business like show business
in the hood they say there's no business like hope in it you
know, they say I talk a little faster if you listen a little fast I
ain't got to slow down for you to catch up,